School playground crazes come and go but the latest collectable toy is proving popular with children and adults alike.
学校操场上的流行热潮此起彼伏，但最新的可收藏玩具被证明同时受到儿童和成年人的欢迎。
My kids have gone mad for the plastic spinning disc called a fidget spinner and I have to admit, I‘ve become a little addicted too - but why?
我的孩子们对那个叫做指尖陀螺的塑料旋转圆盘着了迷，我不得不承认，我也有点上瘾了——但这是为什么呢？
Fidget spinners have taken the world by storm.
指尖陀螺已经风靡全球。
They were originally designed to help kids with conditions like autism deal with stress but they have become a popular toy and they’re helping reduce my stress levels too - when there‘s something on my mind I just spin!
它们最初是为了帮助患有像自闭症这类病症的孩子应对压力而设计的，但它们现在已经成为了一种流行的玩具，而且它们也在帮助我减轻压力——当我有心事的时候，我就转一转！
So what’s the big deal about these three-pronged pieces of rotating plastic?
那么，这些有三个分叉的旋转塑料片有什么了不起的呢？
Well, there are many different designs and colours to collect and then there‘s the challenge of spinning them, getting the speed up, balancing it on the end of your finger.
嗯，有许多不同的设计和颜色可以收藏，而且还有旋转它们的挑战，比如提高转速，在指尖处掌握平衡。
On video-sharing websites, vloggers have amassed millions of views from performing tricks with their fidget spinners.
在视频分享网站上，视频博主们通过用指尖陀螺表演技巧已经积累了数百万的浏览量。
Richard Gottlieb, founder of US-based consultancy Global Toy Experts, says adults are increasingly turning to fidget toys because he says, with all the bad news in the world, “it is a good time to be selling something that allows an individual to fidget off some stress — particularly at a time when smoking is looked down on.”
美国咨询公司“全球玩具专家”的创始人理查德·戈特利布说，成年人越来越多地选择指尖玩具，因为他说，在这个充满坏消息的世界里，“现在是销售一种能让个人缓解一些压力的东西的好时机——尤其是在吸烟被人们鄙视的时候。”
For most school children, they‘ve become the latest ’must-have‘ accessory, although some schools have banned them, saying some are poorly made and can be a distraction for pupils.
对于大多数小学生来说，指尖陀螺已经成为了最新的“必备”配饰，尽管一些学校已经禁止了它们，称有些指尖陀螺制作粗糙，可能会让学生分心。
However, one teacher, Timmons, says they can help some children learn.
然而，一位名叫蒂蒙斯的老师说，它们可以帮助一些孩子学习。
She says: “A fidget toy is something that they can use to channel their energies, without causing a distraction like tapping a pencil or their feet.
她说：“这些指尖玩具是一种让他们可以不停摆弄，而不会像敲铅笔或脚那样造成干扰。
It’s so much less distracting to channel their energies into something else while the teaching is happening.”
在教学进行时将他们的精力引导到其他事情上，这种方式干扰性小得多。”
Fidget spinners join a long and distinguished list of other childhood favourites now living in the teacher‘s top drawer.
指尖陀螺加入了一长串曾经备受孩子们喜爱的物品行列，现在它们都被放在老师的最上面抽屉里。
It wasn’t long ago when our homes and school playgrounds were littered with loom bands as they suddenly became must-have accessories.
不久前，我们的家里和学校操场上还到处都是橡皮筋手环，因为它们突然成了必备的配饰。
Billions of them were sold and then made into various forms of rubbery jewellery.
数十亿个橡皮筋手环被售出，然后被做成了各种橡胶首饰。
One teacher, Guy Tarrant, has confiscated numerous items from children over the years.
一位名叫盖伊·塔兰特的老师多年来从孩子们那里没收了许多东西。
He says: “There‘s so much stuff, so many fads and stages.
他说：“有这么多东西，这么多时尚潮流和阶段。
I worked as a supply teacher in over 150 schools so I’ve probably seen it all.”
我在150多所学校当过代课老师，所以我可能什么都见过了。”
It‘s probably fair to say fidget spinners won’t always be flavour of the month.
可以说，指尖陀螺可能不会一直是风靡一时的东西。
Eventually they‘ll be confined to the bin, to be replaced by a new equally addictive and annoying craze.
最终，它们会被扔进垃圾桶，被一种同样令人上瘾又烦人的新潮流所取代。